Improved Synced by BanglarBagh
I don 't need it . I 'm telling you .
Just because you don 't feel sick now doesn 't mean you don 't need the shot .
I never get sick , okay ? You can take that and give it to Barry .
- His nose is always running . - What are you giving me shit for ?
I saw you earlier today . We said hi . I said , " Cole . " You said , " Mr. Daisy . "
Why are you giving me shit today ? I mean , it 's just a needle , man .
Damn . Come here , get the shot . Ain 't nothing to be scared of .
There 's 62 kids came here , got a shot , no problem .
You come in here , take ten minutes ? I got 84 kids more to go . Okay ?
We 're boys . Be cool . Shit , man . Are you gonna take this shot ?
Step over here and take the shot , just like you 'd take some ass .
There 's nothing to be scared of .
I 'm not scared .
( Cole screaming )
Pussy !
( school bell rings )
MELANIE : Did you know only one baby was born on the Mayflower ?
How crazy is that shit ?
His name was literally Oceanus .
He didn 't even have a nationality .
Just a citizen of the sea , I guess .
What class did you learn that in ?
( scoffs ) No one learns anything in class . That 's why we have the Internet .
( rap music playing over speakers )
( Melanie sighs ) There 's my dad .
MELANIE 'S DAD : Melanie , get over here .
It was his high-school dream car .
He got it after the divorce to make Mom jealous , but ...
- it didn 't work because it 's a car . - MELANIE 'S DAD : Now .
Dad , can we give Cole a ride home ?
Cole , are your parents expecting you to take the bus home ?
- I guess so . - Yeah , they are .
So , you should take the bus , okay , sport ?
Sorry , dude . I 'll see you , though , neighbor , huh ?
- I didn 't ... - What 's that ?
( engine revving )
- NASCAR Nation , bitch . Whoo ! - MELANIE : Dad ...
MELANIE : Dad !
JEREMY : Ooh-whah , ooh-whah . Ooh-whah , ooh-whah .
Well , well , well .
JEREMY : Hey , Colonoscopy . How 's it hanging ?
I don 't know . Okay ?
Well , speaking of hanging , have your balls dropped yet ?
( boys laughing ) ( Cole mumbling )
I didn 't catch that .
I said , " Why are you so interested in my balls ? "
Last thing he cares about is your balls .
JEREMY : Yeah , ' cause on Saturday , I hooked up with Shelly MacEntyre .
The sophomore ?
The sophomore . But in many ways , she was a senior .
- I don 't believe you . - You don 't need to believe him .
It 's not like your belief will validate what happens to his dick .
Wanna know how it was ?
No , not really .
Well , see , as a 14-year-old in that kind of situation
with a 16-year-old that looks like Shelly MacEntyre ,
it was overwhelming , man .
I mean , she is a woman .
Fully-developed , man . It 's crazy , man . It 's ... ( grunts )
Man , you know what I 'm saying ?
I said , do you know what I 'm saying ?
You just said it didn 't matter if I believed you .
- Well , I changed my mind , bitch . - Sorry , I wasn 't ...
JEREMY : Oh , my God . He 's so weird . ( laughs )
Ooh-whah , ooh-whah . Ooh-whah , ooh-whah .
WOMAN : Hey !
Did you just touch Cole ?
- So , what if I did ? - WOMAN : Jeremy , check it out .
You so much as think about Cole again ...
and I 'm gonna ...
( inaudible dialogue )
♪ The girls wanna be her The boys wanna be her ♪
You crazy bitch .
♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
- ( tire hissing ) - Now get out of here !
Before I run you over , you little Pap smear .
- Hey , Coley . - COLE : Hey , Bee .
These are new .
Yeah , I have to wear them sometimes .
They supposedly help strengthen my left eye ,
- but I can 't tell the difference . - You look pretty strong to me .
You skin your palms ?
- It doesn 't hurt . - Yeah , it does . Come here .
- They bother you a lot ? - No .
You look away when you lie , dude . They the ones that egg your house ?
( sighs , clicks tongue ) You gotta punch them in the dick .
And if they 're chasing you , wait until they 've almost got you ,
drop like a bag of rocks , then when they trip over you ,
and they 're on the ground , kick them in the dick .
- Hey , so , tell me , how 's the folks ? - Better , I think .
Hotel therapy 's working ?
( chuckles ) No , come on , it 's great .
I mean , they 're happy , we get to hang out , and I get paid .
- I 'm like your little Protestant . - ( chuckles ) What ?
' Cause , like , I have to pay you to hang out with me .
Are you trying to say " prostitute " ?
Oh , my God ...
No , that would make me the prostitute and your parents the clients .
That is a terrible analogy . That is the worst one ever .
- Oh ... - Besides ,
I 'd wanna hang out with you either way .
Really ?
One hundred percent .
I got two years tops before you 're too cool to hang out with me .
I 'll never be too cool .
BEE : Hey , is that the roof of your tree house ?
COLE : Yeah , we just started to take it down .
I ... I don 't care . I mean , my , uh ...
Tree houses are for kids anyway .
There 's a lot of good memories in there , right ?
Yeah .
All right , tomorrow night . You . Me . Party .
Sounds good .
( gulps )
( Bee grunts )
E.T. fingers .
( both buzzing )
- All right . See you , Cee . - Bye-bye , Bee .
( car door squeaks )
Gotta get that door fixed . You 're still giving this to me , right ?
- One hundred percent . - Can 't have a sticky door on my car .
Hey , Mom !
MOM : Hey ! Cole .
Cole , can you hand me one of those traps , please ?
Ow .
- Thanks . Hi . - Hi .
( grunts ) Thanks , buddy .
( groans ) God . God .
Mom , how can you be under there ? There 's like a trillion spiders .
MOM : Cole , I don 't like it under here . It 's pretty much the worst .
- Do you think I 'm a pussy , Mom ? - ( thud ) Ow .
MOM : Do you know what that word means ?
- COLE : Yeah , like , afraid of everything . - Ow .
Um ...
Huh .
Well ... ( sighs )
I think ... you are at a time in your life
where a lot of things are scary .
But as you get older , those same things will stop frightening you as much .
Okay ?
It 's gonna be okay .
COLE : You should really get some bug spray to kill the spiders in there .
What have they done to you ? They eat other dirty bugs .
Hey , will you get me a lemonade ?
- Yep . - Thanks .
Mom , I know " pussy " also means " vagina . " I 'm not retarded .
Cole Johnson . Do not say " retarded . "
- But I can say " pussy " or " vagi ... " - ( drill whirring )
Don 't say it , okay ?
Go get me a lemonade .
Oh , my God , he said " pussy . "
MAN : Breathe in . Breathe out .
- Unclench that sphincter . - COLE : Okay .
- How those mirrors looking ? - Looking good .
Parking brakes ?
Nope .
- Hands ? - Ten and two .
Engage .
( engine revs , fades )
Dad , did you know that seven teenagers die a day from driving ?
Really ? Wow .
Did you know that , uh , 14 teenagers die a day from over-worrying ?
I went on the Internet ,
and there 's pictures of them . They die like this :
Maybe next week .
All right , buddy , sure . You wanna swap ?
- Yeah . - Good . All right . You did good .
You started the car , you put the seat belt on .
Don 't worry about it , pal . There 's no rush .
It 's okay to be scared . It 's not a big deal , okay ?
Hey , let me ask you something . Do your friends ...
Do they make fun of you for having a babysitter ?
Yeah .
But then they see her and get really jealous .
Yeah . Heck , yeah , they do . ( chuckles )
I don 't know about you , buddy , but I 'm feeling like a cop .
I 'm craving some donuts .
( shouting )
DAD : All right !
( both laughing )
What are you watching ?
Your dad is bingeing on Mad Men .
Again .
You wouldn 't like it .
It 's on HBO ?
- ( chuckles ) - No , it 's not ... It 's not dirty , buddy .
It 's not on HBO .
It 's dense , you know . So , it might go over your head .
When you get a little older , we 'll binge-watch it together .
How about that ?
- COLE : All right . - Cole , will you clean up the toys
in the hallway for me ?
Okay , Mom . Jeez .
Thank you .
COLE : Much cleaner .
Who cares ?
Hey . Oh .
Hey , that doesn 't seem safe at all .
- I can handle it . - Yeah . No , I get it .
Stop . Stop .
And hand me the knife .
Fabulous . Why you cutting up your car with a knife ?
I 'm gonna switch the roof with a fastback ,
- so it 's aerodynamic . - Uh-huh .
It 's gonna give me more downforce on the turns .
When it hits the ramp , it 'll do a barrel roll
and smash into the crash zone exactly how I intend ...
Got it , got it . I applaud your passion for aerodynamics .
I absolutely do , but only use this if you 're cutting a flank steak .
And don 't do that . That 's my job .
And if you take that job , what am I doing at this house ?
Do you want me to put it back ?
DAD : No . I 'm gonna put this in the dishwasher ,
' cause it 's coated in my sweat and fear .
My parents are going away again . I think they go to have sex ,
but it just makes me feel like they go to get away from me .
They 're definitely having sex .
They probably have sex when you 're home , too .
Besides , I bet Bee has boys over at your place all the time doing it .
Nope . No .
No way . Not a chance .
Yeah . That 's what babysitters do .
They put the kids down , sneak their boyfriends in . Doing it .
Seriously , have you ever been awake after she 's fallen asleep ?
I dare you to stay up tonight . You 'll see .
I 'm gonna find out .
- Perv . - No ! I 'm choking !
( Melanie laughing ) ( Cole shouting )
BOY : Pussy !
( school bell rings )
Honey , not that I 'm rushing you , but weren 't we supposed to leave at five ?
MOM : No , honey , 5 : 30 to avoid holiday traffic .
We were supposed to leave at five .
Don 't move the furniture around . We just did the floors .
- I don 't want your mom yelling . - COLE : Got it .
I don 't yell at you . I just speak in all caps .
Right . That 's what I love about her .
- ( doorbell rings ) - Here . Get that . It 's probably Bee .
COLE : Okay .
- MOM : Can you hurry up ? - DAD : Yes .
( exhales deeply )
- What up , Cee ? - What up , Bee ?
( both buzzing )
- MOM : Hey , Bee . How are you ? - Oh , you know , can 't complain .
- MOM : Good . - Where to this weekend ?
- Uh ... The Hyatt . Living large . - Mm !
DAD : Can 't find it !
Uh , try the bottom drawer under your Invisalign .
Um , anyway , you know the drill .
No violent movies , no junk food , bed by ten .
- COLE : Mom . - Bed by 10 : 30 ?
- COLE : You serious ? - BEE : Anything else ?
Uh , there is not a bathing suit in that bedroom .
MOM : Then , honey , I don 't know what to tell you .
- I 'm not up there . - DAD : Okay .
( sighs )
- He 's totally gonna bring his jean shorts . - COLE : Mom , he calls them jorts .
- Well , we 'll be fine . I can handle him . - I know . You 're the best .
- DAD : I 'm bringing my jorts . - MOM : I knew it !
- DAD : I 'm bringing my jorts . - I knew it . Great .
I will be the envy of women everywhere .
Hey , uh , Bee , call us if there 's any trouble , okay ?
- Cole , don 't cause any trouble . - COLE : Dad , I know .
You know what , honey ?
- You got your flu shot , so no exertion . - COLE : Mom .
- Yeah , no running around . Board games . - COLE : Got it . Okay ?
Hey , Cole , remember , you 're the man of the house now .
That 's sweet . You are .
- We love you . Bye , Bee . - I love you . Have fun .
- DAD : But not too much fun . - MOM : Not too much .
( Foghat 's " I Just Want to Make Love to You " playing )
♪ I don 't want you cook my bread ♪
♪ I don 't want you make my bed ♪
♪ I don 't want you to be true ♪
♪ I just want to make love to you ♪
♪ I don 't want you be no slave ♪
♪ I don 't want you to be sad and blue ♪
♪ I just want to make love to you ♪
COLE : No way you 're gonna beat my dive .
So , you 're basically saying , intergalactic dream team on a mission .
- Yeah . So , there 's an epic villain , right ? - Right .
Okay , so , you have to fill a starship ...
full of the best people or aliens or robots to take them down .
- How many seats have I got ? - Five .
- Five ? - Six , if you need , like , a duo .
But you can 't have a Predator and Xenomorph .
They 'd fight . The mission would be futile .
No , no , okay , I get it .
All right . One ... Kirk .
Two , Picard .
Three , Will Smith and Jeff Goldblum from Independence Day .
Five , Ripley , and six ... Are you ready for this shit ?
A Xenomorph egg .
- No way . - Yeah .
Yes . Yes . Okay . Here 's the plan .
Kirk and Picard team up to captain , then when they get close ,
they send Will and Goldblum to get inside the lair .
- They have experience with that . - Fair .
Now , this whole time , Ripley 's been bitching
about the Xenomorph egg and shit , ' cause that 's her move .
But she 's gotta do this .
- It 's the only way to save the world . - The universe .
Right ! Exactly !
So , Will and Goldblum get her inside the lair .
Ripley personally drops off the egg , the facehugger attacks the big bad !
Ripley makes it back to Will and Goldblum , the big bad attacks them ,
they narrowly escape .
Kirk and Picard supply cover as the spacecraft returns home ,
then they peace out of there . Meanwhile , the big bad starts feeling like shit ...
( groaning ) ( both shouting )
He 's out !
Who said he was a he ?
- Shut up . A woman just saved the galaxy . - Are facehuggers female ?
No , ' cause they got dicks .
Oh , so , you 're saying it took a dick to save the galaxy .
- I want a do-over . - ( grunts )
- I want a do-over . - No do-overs .
Come on . Aliens don 't abide by our primitive gender stereotypes .
- What 's done is done . - You suck .
- You suck , and I hope you die . - You couldn 't live without me .
It would definitely affect my income . So , you 're probably right .
( timer dings )
- Pizza ! - Pizza !
BEE AND ACTOR 1 : Big Indian Chief . So special . So above the law .
I told you , you 'd make a mistake , and I 'd be waiting .
COLE AND ACTOR 2 : It doesn 't look like I have any choice , does it ?
( Bee and actor 1 laugh ) That 's right . You don 't .
COLE AND ACTOR 2 : I 'm gonna take this right foot ...
and I 'm gonna whop you on that side of your face .
And you wanna know something ?
There 's not a damn thing you 're gonna be able to do about it .
- BEE AND ACTOR 1 : Really ? - COLE AND ACTOR 2 : Really .
BEE AND ACTOR 1 : Kill that Indian son of a bitch .
( grunting and shouting )
( both laughing )
Think my parents are gonna get a divorce ?
I don 't know , man . I hope not .
Melanie 's parents got divorced . Her mom lives with her boyfriend .
That 's gross .
Isn 't that the cute chick across the street ?
Ms. Dryer is not cute . She 's gross .
Her boyfriend 's like 20 .
Not her . Melanie .
I wouldn 't say she 's cute .
Oh , I would . I would say she 's super-duper cute .
( stammers ) I see what you 're trying to do . It 's not gonna work .
Whatever . You want your tongues to touch .
Nope . No way .
- Oh , you 're in denial . - You 're an ... asshole .
( laughing )
Oh , my God . That was so great .
But you 'll be all right if your parents break up .
I mean ... you just gotta take care of yourself .
Gotta figure out what you want , and then do what you can to get it .
( Cole sighs )
( both chuckle )
Ah , shit , dude , it 's super late .
- I 'm not tired . - Well , I know you 're not . I am .
( snaps fingers ) If I give you a shot , will you go to bed ?
- I don 't know , maybe . - I 'll make it a double .
- You 'll sleep like a rock . - Okay .
Here you are , my good sir .
Don 't say a word of this to your parents .
My dad lets me drink Mike 's all the time .
Dude , that is the coolest thing I 've ever heard in my life .
You 're not gonna do it with me ?
All right , sure . I 'll be right back .
( coughing )
You did it without me ?
Cheers .
Whew .
- MELANIE : ( on phone ) She 's getting laid . - ( chuckles )
- I 'm gonna find out . - Wow , I 'm impressed .
That 's actually pervy , though , watching people do it .
I 'm not a perv . I just wanna know what happens after I go to sleep .
I gotta go .
( phone beeps )
- No . - ( footsteps approaching )
( knock on door )
Enter .
You sleepy ?
Yeah , I 'm really tired .
Well , rest up . The party continues tomorrow .
You need anything ? All right .
- Bee ? - Yeah ?
Thanks for knowing me and treating me like I was okay .
You don 't think you 're okay ?
I mean ...
I wanna feel normal , but ...
I just feel weird most of the time .
Well , I like weird .
All of the time .
So , just imagine how all the girls are gonna love you when you 're a senior .
( sniffles )
See you in the morning .
Good night , dude .
( doorbell rings )
( people chattering nearby )
Ew . Orgy ?
Orgy ?
( woman moaning on phone )
( indistinct chattering )
MAN : Spin it .
ALLISON : Whoo !
- MAX : Yeah ! - JOHN : We lit . We lit .
Truth me .
Out of everybody here , who would you want to sleep with the most ?
- Sonya . - ALLISON : Ooh , yeah .
( laughing )
Hundred percent .
- Come on . - Sam , you 're a close second , stud .
- JOHN : Damn . - Okay . My turn .
( Max grunts )
- ALLISON : Yo , people . - JOHN : To this bad girl .
Bee , truth or dare .
Dare .
( all shout )
- I dare you to kiss everyone here . - ( Allison chuckles )
- Yes . - ALLISON : Ooh , yeah .
- JOHN : She got balls . - SONYA : I need to watch .
( Sonya chuckling )
All right .
- That 's what I 'm talking about . - SONYA : I 'm excited for that .
- MAX : That 's all I 'm looking for . - ALLISON : Hold on .
JOHN : Let 's go .
I 'm ready .
♪ Everybody loves the sunshine ♪
( in deep voice ) I know it was you , Fredo . I know it was you .
( all laughing )
- Thank you . - Is that Lord of the Rings ?
That was The Godfather Part II .
I love her .
( all laughing )
- BEE : All right , this is easy . Come on . - MAX : That was pretty good .
( Bow Wow Wow 's " I Want Candy " playing )
MAX : Oh , okay .
JOHN : Y 'all rehearsed this .
♪ Go to see him when the sun goes down ♪
♪ Ain 't no finer boy in town ♪
♪ You 're my guy What the doctor ordered ♪
♪ So sweet you make my mouth water ♪
♪ I want candy ♪
♪ Yeah ! ♪
( pants ) Wait , just give me ...
Give me a second to process that shit .
- JOHN : You raised by Rick James ? - I 'm thinking a redo .
- That 's amazing . - ( laughing )
Make sure it 's real nice and long for you , because I 'm black . See that ?
There you go . Mm .
- ( Bee giggles ) - Fuck , yeah .
Come on .
( Allison laughing )
- Whoo ! - SONYA : Yeah !
JOHN : Oh , Bee !
( all laughing ) ( John groans )
Bee , what the hell ?
You give her that romantic shit , and you 're gonna lick my face ?
Damn , that 's all I 'm asking .
- BEE : All right . - JOHN : Freaky shit .
Smell good . The spit is nice . Brushed your teeth this morning .
( Max laughing ) Okay .
- JOHN : Weird . - BEE : Hi .
- ( John howling ) - ( Allison laughing ) Yeah !
( Max cat-calling ) Sammy 's turn .
- ( John laughing ) - ( Max chanting ) Sammy .
- ALLISON : She 's so hot . - JOHN : Okay .
MAX : Come on , Sam . You got this .
Make out with her .
SAM : I 'm sorry .
This is kind of weird . I don 't even really know you guys .
MAX : Come on , Sam . Freak you out , there , stud ?
- Sam , don 't be a puss . - SAM : I don 't even know you guys .
SAM : I 'm not . I 'm ... I just ...
- You 're staring at me . - MAX : Oh , we 're not looking .
ALLISON : Hey , it 's not weird .
- BEE : Hey . - JOHN : Yeah .
Just close your eyes .
Okay ?
Pretend they 're not even here .
You can do this .
You got this .
( hushes )
Just because I close my eyes doesn 't mean that they 're not here .
Do you trust me ?
Yes .
Just relax .
It 's not weird , okay ? We 're just having fun .
( John howls )
There he goes .
( John chuckles )
( screaming )
Shh .
You 're helping fulfill a great purpose . Know this .
I don 't wanna fulfill a great porpoise .
( grunts ) Did he just say " porpoise " ?
Yo , I think he did .
He didn 't even get a chance to understand .
( panting )
Ready ?
- SONYA : Ready . - Yep .
- ( John grunts ) Oh , okay . - ( exhales )
JOHN : That shit leaking .
Wait , hold on . My shit ain 't working . I think it ran out of blood .
- Oh , shit ! - Oh , shit .
( John yells ) Oh , shit !
MAX : All that blood was just in his boner .
Max , don 't laugh , okay ? John , relax . This blood is serving you .
I did not sign up for this shit to serve me in my mouth .
This shit 's still warm . I think he got a fever .
You know what you signed up for . You want to go platinum , John ?
Things can get messy when you make a deal with the devil .
Now collect it .
- JOHN : Like this ? - BEE : There you go .
ALLISON : How long is this gonna take ? I just want my shit to come true .
BEE : Allison , you 'll all get what you want .
Okay , let 's go .
JOHN : I don 't think this is funny . Look at my outfit .
I just got this shit , you feel me ? Thirty percent off .
Macy 's . Top rack . I don 't play games .
You look like Carrie ,
- but black . - Carrie would 've been better black .
She would have been covered in Hennessy , all right ?
What are you wearing ? Looking like Big Bird 's side bitch .
I just came from a game . That 's why I 'm wearing this , obviously .
I was not gonna miss this .
Look at this shit . That would go viral so hard .
I mean , nobody 's done human sacrifice .
People have always done human sacrifice .
Yeah , but , like ... not in America with hot people .
Sonya , get the cases .
Listen , when you 're done being totally useless ,
get a rag and wipe Sacrifice Samuel out my damn eye . OMG .
Hey .
Nice one , John .
( gasps ) Oh , my God .
I 've got Sacrifice Samuel all over me .
What 's in the box ?
Yo , so , Bee , why do you need the book if you already know what to do ?
It 's like Jesus asking directions to heaven .
Just fucking go up , you know ?
Well , the Jews have their scrolls ,
Christians have their Bibles ,
and the devil has his verses .
Don 't touch it . It 's very old and very delicate .
It 's the only one .
You recite the verse while the blood hits the page .
Without it , none of this happens .
Let 's get started before we head upstairs and get the blood of the innocent .
( gasps )
WOMAN : 911 , what 's your emergency ?
My name is Cole Johnson . A guy was murdered in my living room .
The address is , uh ... 2455 Bigby Drive .
- Can you please send someone ? - Are the attackers still in the house ?
They 're downstairs having a blast .
- How many are there , Cole ? - Too many .
Can you please get my mom ? She 's at the Hyatt in the city .
Living large .
Of course , Cole . Now listen to me . It 's important that you stay hidden .
- I gotta protect myself . Thanks . - Do not do that . No , no , no ...
- Okay . - ( chattering )
BEE : ... we shed about 15 percent of our dead cells .
JOHN : Whoo !
Yo , this kid 's hobby must be getting bullied .
He 's reading The Secret ?
He 's ten years old . What secret he need to know ?
Won 't he hear us ?
With the amount of drugs I gave him ? Hell , no .
- SONYA : Good boy . Pretty boy . - Do you have the needle ?
Of course , I have the needle .
You know , there is a faster way to get all that blood .
BEE : What happens when you kill someone ?
JOHN : They lose , like , all they Instagram followers .
- ( gasps ) Oh , my God , that would suck . - No , they die .
And then I 'd have to find another innocent kid .
And all of this only works if we get that top-shelf pure shit .
And Cole is basically a faucet of that for us .
BEE : After this , we finish the ritual ...
and your wish comes true .
- Damn , I missed the vein . - SONYA : Mm .
BEE : Premium real estate . Go for it .
( Sonya incanting )
Wait , you gotta give him a Band-Aid .
Okay . Let 's go mix some blood .
John , alley-oop .
JOHN : LeBron James .
Good boy .
( panting )
Why is he shirtless ?
- That 's your first question ? - How can you ask that ? Just look at him .
I still don 't get it .
( grunting )
Give him a cookie .
- No , thanks . - Eat the cookie .
I just don 't really like cookies , okay ? Bee knows that .
You 'll feel better if you eat . You fainted .
No , I didn 't .
Yes , you did .
After I took your blood ,
I waited in the room , because something felt off .
I crouched behind the door . A few seconds later , you got up ,
tied a sheet to your bed , threw the sheet out the window .
And then you fainted . So , you know ...
Your blood sugar is low . Eat the cookie .
Are you mad at me ?
Cookie .
This is gonna be so good .
What the ...
Oh , there you go .
There you go .
That 's a good boy .
- Why are you awake , Cole ? - Because I couldn 't sleep .
- I don 't believe you . - COLE : Okay , fine . I ...
I was gonna go smoke in the woods .
BEE : You were gonna go smoke in the woods .
Yeah . You know , like ... marijuana .
You weren 't gonna share with your boy ? Come on , man .
We could 've got high , listen to my mix tape . My shit 's fire .
- I wanna smoke pot . - Why didn 't you drink the shot ?
Why is he shirtless ? Why did you take my blood ?
- Cole . - Okay . Fine . Because I don 't like alcohol .
I just drank it because I wanted you to think I was cool .
Why did you give a 12-year-old alcohol ?
' Cause I put shit in that alcohol that makes them conk out
for eight hours or more .
What else did you see ?
I just see you .
And these assholes , who I don 't know , in my house .
- Why is his shirt covered in blood ? - No one would let me borrow a shirt .
- That 's not even an answer . - Oh , my God .
Does he not see the mirror behind him ? We can see you cutting the rope .
Well , he does now .
Aw , it 's so cute , you 're still cutting the rope .
Look at you . You 're really trying there , aren 't you ?
- Why are you cutting ropes ? - I don 't like being tied up .
- Why do you have a knife ? - It was a gift .
Oh , my God .
He 's still cutting the ropes .
Determined little fucker , aren 't you ?
Look , I won 't tell anyone .
Okay ? You know me . I 'm good with secrets .
I won 't tell my parents that you were having an orgy
and needed my blood to do it .
( John and Allison laughing )
Do you even know what an orgy is ?
I 'm guessing it 's something sad people do
' cause they want other sad people to like them ,
and they can forget for one minute how sad they are in general .
That 's actually a pretty good answer .
It was for a science project , okay ?
The orgy ?
No . The blood .
Orgy is when a bunch of people have sex together .
We wouldn 't need your blood for that .
You could 've just asked .
I would 've let you have some blood for science .
I knew you were afraid of needles .
This was clearly a misunderstanding .
Sonya , untie him .
I 'm sorry we scared you , Cole . We good ?
( police sirens wailing )
- JOHN : Oh , shit . - ( screaming )
- MAX : Shut up ! - Holy fuck !
- Not good . - Fucking police .
Why are the cops outside , Cole ?
- I don 't know . - Did you call them ?
- No . You said you were in the room . - Makes me think you saw something
that scared you enough to call the cops . Right , Cole ?
- ( knock on door ) - Oh , fuck !
Answer me , Cole .
Help ! Help ! I 'm tied up inside ! They 're about ...
( grunts ) Ow .
- Oh , shit ! - OFFICER : Everybody , freeze !
OFFICER 2 : Hands up , now ! Put your hands up ! Now !
- Now ! - MAX : Here we go .
-
OFFICER : Hands up ! - JOHN : Oh !
( screaming )
- ( chuckles ) -
OFFICER : Shit !
Hands up . Don 't shoot , man . Black lives matter , too . You feel me ?
ALLISON : Bee !
- Oh ! - MAX : Oh , shit !
Titty gone !
Don 't you move . Keep your hands up . Nobody move !
- ( screams ) - Don 't you move .
JOHN : Chill with the gun stuff .
Chill . You Mexican , right ? Look , I speak Spa ...
Lo siento , my nigga , lo siento .
( shouting )
- Are you serious ? - ( laughing )
( screaming )
JOHN : Max , what you doing , man ?
- JOHN : Max , what you doing , man ? - No , no , no !
- ( officer 2 shouting ) - Oh .
( grunting )
No !
Harder .
( screaming )
Whoo !
Look , man . Three out of four people got an STD .
I got two people 's blood on me .
You do the math . I got AIDS . I know I got AIDS .
You killed him !
- Kind of your fault , bud . - Are you insane ?
No , Cole . I 'm just trying ...
MAN : ( on radio ) What 's the status of that 187 call on Bigby Drive ?
JOHN : Look , man .
I can 't go to jail . Y 'all killed the cops , man .
I ain 't involved with this shit .
It 's fine . Max , pick it up .
( Max chuckles )
JOHN : It 's the statistics .
They say you either end up in jail or dead .
It 's gonna be both for me , Bee .
- What 's the code for " all clear " ? - MAN : What 's your status ?
Just say " all clear . "
SONYA : Why would he know cop codes ?
( Cole shouts )
Stop screaming and act like an adult .
What 's the code ? I know you know it .
Little boy here a nerd . Tell them the codes .
What 's the code ?
- Ten-fifty-three . - JOHN : Punch that shit in .
- MAN : Bynak , you there ? - Wait .
BEE : You don 't get it . You look away when you lie .
You look me in the eyes and tell me the truth .
What is the code for " all clear " ?
It 's 10-4 . Obviously .
What 's " we 're taking a break to get food " ?
- COLE : Say we 're taking a break to ... - BEE : Cole .
MAN : Officer Bynak , you need backup ?
Code seven .
Ten-four , all clear . We 're code seven .
MAN : Ten-four . Enjoy your double-double .
Should 've been a cop .
( screaming )
Shit .
( groaning ) Ow , ow !
ALLISON : Oh , my God . Guys .
Oh , my God !
Fucking help me . What are you doing ?
Oh , my God . He shot me in the boob .
What kind of dick shoots a girl in the boob ?
- I did not sign up for this shit . - Stop complaining . Stop all your whining .
They 're totally gonna stop growing . They weren 't even done .
Sometimes you gotta settle , all right ?
I got a cousin Chantelle , titties flat .
Personality real good .
Ow . Oh , my God .
- Ow ! You fucking bitch . - ( Sonya laughs )
What 's wrong with you ?
- Get away from me with your fucking beret . - She 's gonna bleed out .
What ? No .
What do you mean , I 'm gonna bleed ?
Can we just stick a tampon in it or something ?
Oh , my God . We need to call an ambulance , guys .
I need an ambulance . I don 't wanna lose my boob .
I can 't do that .
ALLISON : What ?
Why not ?
Because your boob was shot by a now-dead cop .
Have fun explaining that .
No dude 's gonna motorboat these , Bee .
( crying ) ( mimicking motorboat )
How you like it ? You want them quick or you want them long ?
( continues mimicking motorboat ) You want a little spit on them ?
BEE : Cole !
-
ALLISON : Oh , my God . - JOHN : Hey , hey , hey .
Who 's gonna want to suck on my nipples ?
No one .
JOHN : Cole . Come here , Cole . Stop running .
Come here , little baby . Yeah . Come here , buddy .
Just wanna talk . Just wanna talk .
Son of a bitch .
Hey , this ain 't Home Alone . Hey , hey , hey .
Oh , shit .
( exhales )
Right in the jugular . Yeah ! ( chuckles )
( gasps )
- Get him . - I got him .
I 'm gonna kill you with my bare hands .
Whoo !
- Now I gotta clean this up . - MAX : Run , Cole !
I 'm coming for you .
Open the door , Cole .
No locked doors , Cole !
Open the door . We just wanna talk , Cole .
Come on , Cole !
( panting )
Hey , Coley . How 's it hanging ?
( fabric stretching )
Please , don 't kill me . Please .
No . You 're gonna kill me . No .
Max . It 's okay , Max . Please .
Got you .
Ow !
Whoa . Deep breaths , buddy .
( coughs , groans )
MAX : I 'm right on your ass , Coley !
Keep moving !
Come on , Cole !
Where are you , you little shit ?
Cole .
Coley .
( panting )
( shouts )
There 's a dead guy ...
I 'm sorry .
( shouting )
Okay . Okay . Okay .
Bug spray . Blanket .
Lighter .
Whoa . The Fat Dragon .
MAX : Coley !
Cole !
Come out and play !
( Cole panting )
( footsteps above )
( Sonya whispers ) Is this where you are ?
( laughing )
( Sonya hums )
( creaking )
( shouts )
Are you right ... here ?
Good boy .
( gasps )
Beautiful boy .
So soft , so pretty .
MAX : Coley !
- Where 's Cole ? - SONYA : Ugh .
MAX : Sonya , bring your cookies and help me find this little fuck .
SONYA : I 'm coming .
( whimpers )
Hi , Cole .
Oh , God .
How long do you think it 'll take your parents
to find your body down here ? ( chuckles )
Tomorrow ?
Two days from now ?
Even later ?
Probably when your body starts to reek like cheese .
( laughs ) Or we could just burn your body , Cole .
It would be so beautiful .
( Sonya screams )
( laughs ) Oh , you missed .
My nails !
Cole ! Cole ! ( grunts )
( thuds ) ( grunts )
I 'm gonna make sure you hurt before you die , Cole .
Cut your fingers off . Every single one .
Come here , Cole !
I 'm making a human self-centipede . Yeah !
Human self-centipede , child !
Gonna taste so good , Cole !
Your mouth is gonna get sewn to your ass , Cole !
Your mouthy ass !
( screaming )
( Sonya continues screaming )
I 'm still alive motherfuck ...
( loud bang )
( gasping )
( coughing )
( applauding )
Did you just blow up Sonya ?
No .
I mean , I 'm not even mad . I 'm a little surprised .
What did that ?
A firework .
A firework ?
Holy shit .
Damn , good for you , kid .
That is awesome .
So , you want a head start ?
- Come on , you 're the quarterback . - Life 's not fair , dude .
You guys suck .
You just blew up Sonya .
You can 't outrun me , Cole .
Wait until they 've almost got you , drop like a bag of rocks .
( Max grunts )
BEE : Kick him in the dick .
Dick .
( Max groans )
Whoo !
You missed my dick .
- No , I didn 't . - Pretty sure you did .
And I got a big dick .
No , you don 't .
That 's just hurtful .
( shouting )
Please , don 't ... Don 't ...
( gasping )
MAX : No whining .
Save some dignity .
( egg breaking )
- What the hell is that ? - ( gasping )
- Huh ? - It 's Jeremy .
- What ? - Eggs .
Eggs .
Eggs ?
You gotta be shitting me .
Somebody 's egging your house ?
( crowd cheering )
MAX : Who is this kid ?
Just an asshole .
- He egg your house a lot ? - Sometimes .
- MAX : So , what are you gonna do about it ? - What ?
I said , are you gonna let that little punk come on to your property ,
your family 's property and disrespect you like that ?
No . Hell , no . This is America . You need to wreck his ass .
Are you kidding me ?
Get out there and crush that bitch .
Go .
( chuckles ) Well , well , well .
It 's Cole sore .
I like your pajamas .
- Thanks . My mom made them . - ( scoffs )
You wanna do something ?
You know what I 'm gonna do ?
What 's that ?
I 'm gonna take this right foot ,
and I 'm gonna whop you on that side of your face .
And there 's not a damn thing you can do about it .
( chuckles ) Really ?
Really .
I 'm gonna wreck your ass .
( grunts )
What the hell was that ? You must be crazy .
Jeremy , you have to listen to me , okay ?
There 's a guy over there who 's trying to kill me .
- I swear to God . - I swear to God .
- I 'm serious . - I 'm serious .
There are dead bodies in my house .
- Wait , seriously ? - The cops came . They killed the cops .
- Where is the cop car ? - They 're crazy . They 're covering it up .
Okay ? If you get me out of this , I 'll wear a blue headband .
I 'll give you foot massages . I 'll do your homework until college .
Oh , okay , okay .
I 'll help you .
- Really ? - Yeah .
I mean , if you die , who am I gonna pick on ?
Exactly .
Okay , so , here 's the plan .
On three , we 're gonna make a run for my bike .
- You 're gonna ride in the back . All right ? - Thank you .
One , two ...
( Jeremy laughing )
Have fun getting murdered , colon cancer .
Ooh-whah , ooh-whah .
You talk too much .
Crack him in the face next time .
Not bad . At least you stood up for yourself .
You gonna let me go now ?
( Max laughs )
( sighs )
No .
But if you kill me , you won 't get what you want .
No , I 'm not like the others .
I came here to kill people .
Yes ! That 's what I 'm talking about , Cole !
Come on , buddy ! Whoo !
Come on , Coley .
Come on , buddy . I 'm right behind you . Move your ass , Cole .
Whoo !
Coming for you .
- ( Cole screams ) - Whoo !
Come on , buddy . Get moving .
( Max laughs )
Come on , buddy .
Let 's go !
Come on ! Get up there ! Come on !
( singsong ) Coley .
Come down and play .
( grunting )
Coley .
Come on , Cole .
Chi-chi-chi , chi-chi-chi , ah
Stuck in the tree .
No way down !
Coley .
( panting )
( gasping ) Where is he ?
( screams )
( in normal voice ) You 're a badass kid .
Relax , Max .
You don 't have to do this .
Well , I kind of have to do this .
Don 't worry . I 'm not gonna let you die with egg on your face .
You poor bastard .
You deserve better than this .
Tonight you get an honorable death .
Tonight you die a man .
I don 't wanna die a man .
( both grunting )
( Max grunts )
( Cole shouts )
( gunshot )
Why are there guns ?
( gun cocks )
( gunshot )
Come here . Come here .
- Was that a gun ? - I got the two guys and the Asian girl .
- The cheerleader got shot . It 's just Bee . - What is going on ?
Bee murdered the geek . Stole my blood . Tied me up . Killed the cops .
- You 're really freaking me out . - I 'm ... sorry .
Bee is bad ?
Yeah . Bee is bad .
- Where 's your dad ? - Out with some Protestant .
- But his car 's here . - She picked him up . He 's really desperate .
Am I the only one that still has a babysitter ?
Yeah .
- So , what do we do ? - Pray .
- Okay . - I was kidding .
- Oh . - But it 's probably a great idea , though .
( both gasp )
Come on .
- You think she can get in here ? - Not if it 's locked .
COLE : Your door automatically locks , right ?
MELANIE : Nope .
( gasps )
( phone buzzes and jingle plays )
( gun cocks )
( pants )
- I shouldn 't have gotten you into this . - You were being shot at .
Especially because I was being shot at .
You 're my best friend , I 'm sorry . I 'm gonna take care of this .
- Do you have your phone ? - Yeah .
- Call the cops . Tell them it 's a 10-53 . - Why do you know cop codes ?
Because I used to wanna be a cop when I grew up .
You never told me that .
I know . I only told Bee .
( Dusty Springfield 's " Spooky " playing )
Are you okay ?
I 've had a really bad night .
♪ And then I stop ♪
♪ And say " all right " ♪
♪ Love is kind of crazy With a spooky little boy like you ♪
Uh ... The last guy I saw get kissed got stabbed in the head by two knives .
♪ You always keep me guessing ♪
♪ I never seem to know What you 're thinking ♪
Just because she 's a psychopath doesn 't mean women are evil .
I know that .
I wish all girls were like you .
♪ And then you smile ♪
( chuckles softly )
I 'm gonna put an end to this .
What are you doing ?
- Keeping you safe . - The lock is on the inside , dumbass .
That was sweet of you .
I 'm really excited we kissed .
Me , too . Let 's make out next time .
Okay . Bye .
Come and get me , Bee !
I 'm right here !
It 's just you and me !
What , you 're gonna get shy now ? !
I 'm going towards my house !
I 'm right here , Bee !
I 'm right here !
What the hell ?
Oh , my God . Where is everything ?
( panting )
( floor creaking )
Oh , my God .
( board creaks )
( gasping )
( gasps )
" Sacrifice ... Get your dreams ... "
( both grunting )
- Get off me ! - I 'm gonna kill you !
I 'm gonna kill you !
Oh , my God !
What 's wrong with you , you little pervert ?
What ? You can 't make me feel bad because I defended myself .
I knew you wanted me this whole time , upstairs in your little room jerking off .
- You 're just sick . - You were trying to kill me .
I wasn 't trying to kill you by punching your dick .
( shouts ) I 've never felt so violated before .
Oh , God .
I only signed up for this dumb shit so I could have my dream job .
And instead , what do I have now , huh ?
This .
One deflated , ugly boob . ( scoffs )
( sobbing ) My life is basically over .
I ... I mean ... you 're still super hot .
What kind of job do you want ?
Journalist .
See , that 's perfect .
Because you 're super smart , and you 're hot ,
- and really driven . - Thank you .
I could be wrong , but I don 't think it would be hard for you
to have a cool life .
Really ?
You think so ? You think maybe we could walk out of this whole thing ?
Just call the police and just , you know , forget this ever happened ?
Yeah .
Exactly .
Do you think I give a fuck what you 're talking about ?
( Allison screams )
COLE : Knife . Where 's the knife ?
Oh ! Dishwasher .
Mom .
Are you the one that put the knife in the dishwasher ?
I think so .
Can you not do that ? It goes in the butcher block .
Yoo-hoo !
Looking for this ?
You still think I 'm pretty ?
( yells )
Oh , you think I 'm scared of a little fire , huh ?
You are dying .
You , you are dying .
You ruined my life .
And now , I 'm gonna ruin yours !
( screams ) ( gunshot )
Holy shit .
( groans )
I found this in the cop car . That was so graphic .
( pants )
She was so annoying .
I wanna throw up .
You and me both .
Where 's Sonya ?
Blown up . Crawlspace . Where are the cops ?
Ditched them with the car .
Now I gotta skip town again .
And that leaves you , and what to do with you .
- Any suggestions ? - Are you gonna shoot me ?
No .
No . I was just shooting around you , ' cause I thought you 'd put your hands up .
I will burn your book !
Cole .
- Cole , listen to me . - No .
- Cole , listen to me . - No , Bee ! You listen to me !
I 've been hunted , you 've stolen my blood , killed people ,
shot at me , and just been general assholes all night .
So , I wanna know what the hell 's going on .
Cole , you 're too young to understand , okay ? Just trust me .
Fuck you !
Cole .
No . You know what ? You deserved that .
What , just because I 'm 12 means I get to be treated like total shit
by you and Jeremy and everyone else ?
You know what ? You 're Don Draper from Mad Men .
How he 's all cool and handsome and everybody loves him ,
then he goes home and you find out he has a wife the whole time .
- He 's such a piece of shit ! - Did you just ruin Mad Men for me ?
It 's not even on anymore . You 'll live .
Still .
- What happens when you leave here ? - What do you mean ?
- I will burn this ! - Okay .
Cole ... what do you want to know ?
What 's the blood for ?
You mix the blood of the innocent with the blood of someone sacrificed ,
recite the verses ,
while dripping it on the page .
And , basically , you get whatever you want .
I used to be so small ... and so scared .
Now I 'm strong ... and I 'm confident ...
and that 's all I ever wanted .
And , so , that 's all I was to you .
You just used me to get what you wanted .
No .
No , Cole . I chose you .
I mean , I could 've shot you and not Allison ,
but I didn 't . I chose you .
' Cause you 're the best .
We click , right ? You 're my guy .
I 'm not the first kid , am I ?
No .
And you 'll leave here and just find another faucet .
- You heard that ? - I heard everything . This is my house .
Okay .
Okay , yes .
And tonight sucked , but we can start again .
So , you have a plan ?
Yeah . We just say they attacked us .
I got him .
Whoo !
Plus , dude , we would have so much fun .
Just you and me against the whole world .
No one will ever hurt you ever again .
There 'll be nothing left to be afraid of . Isn 't that what you wanted ?
What do you say , Cole ?
I guess ...
I guess I have a plan , too .
No !
( Bee screaming )
( Queen 's " We are the Champions " playing ) ♪ I 've paid my dues ♪
BOY : Pussy !
♪ Time after time ♪
- When you 're ready , you 're ready . - A lot of things are scary .
♪ I 've done my sentence ♪
You gotta figure out what you want ...
- and then do what you can to get it . - Keys ...
- Cole ! - ( engine revving )
Ten . Two .
♪ And I need to go on and on And on and on ♪
♪ We are the champions My friends ♪
♪ And we 'll keeping on fighting Till the end ♪
Yeah !
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪ No time for losers ♪
♪ ' Cause we are the champions ♪
( Cole screaming )
( grunting and panting )
What up , Cee ?
You drove a car into your house .
I really didn 't see that coming .
( coughing )
You never told me ...
your intergalactic dream team .
You didn 't ask .
I should have .
I 'm usually pretty good at that stuff .
Admiral Adama to lead .
Data for his intelligence and cool head .
Predator to fight .
Then me and you .
( chuckles )
You didn 't say we could add ourselves .
It 's science fiction . You can do anything .
Well ... I guess that 's true .
But don 't you get it yet ?
I am the big bad .
I loved you .
I don 't care about your dumb book or your stupid cult .
I 'm an adult ...
because when I realized you were the big bad ...
and you betrayed me
and were just gonna hurt other kids ,
I drove a stolen car through you .
( sobbing )
That , I 'll give you . ( chuckles )
I 'll see you , Cee .
Goodbye .
( chuckles )
( sirens wailing )
-
MELANIE 'S DAD : Martinez . - Yeah ?
Protect and serve , idiot .
- MELANIE : It 's just a car . - Protect my car .
Just a car ? ! Just a car ? !
Do not ... Put your hand down right now .
- I thought you were gonna drive away . - I couldn 't leave you .
That was such a douche car .
Melanie , get over here .
Get back here . Now .
Bye .
MELANIE 'S DAD : Oh , my God .
Did you just put your face on him ? Wanna go get tattoos now ?
Yo . What happened ?
Dude , Cole stole a car .
Rammed his house . Killed , like , 50 people .
Fifty people . ( scoffs )
JEREMY : Hey , let 's get out of here .
Today , y 'all . Let 's go .
The hell ?
( tires screeching )
Cindy .
- MOM : Do you have my son ? Please ... - DAD : Cole .
MOM : Honey . Honey . Oh , my God .
Are you okay ? Are you ... ?
- I 'm okay . - DAD : Are you all right ?
- Oh , my God . What happened ? - Is that blood ?
Hey . What happened ?
I don 't need a babysitter anymore .
♪ When my best friend said She had lost her man ♪
♪ To her babysitter I thought she was lying ♪
♪ I said , " No 16-year-old schoolgirl ♪
♪ Would ever take a man of mine " ♪
♪ Staying home With our baby all the time ♪
♪ It kept me kind of brokenhearted ♪
♪ So I went And hired myself a babysitter ♪
♪ And that 's when my trouble all started ♪
♪ This 16-year-old chick walked in ♪
♪ With a skirt up to her waist ♪
♪ She had a truckload of you-know-what ♪
♪ And all of it in place ♪
♪ I should have been aware , mm-hmm ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh , of the babysitter ♪
♪ Oh , yeah , yeah I should 've known from the jump , yeah ♪
♪ She was a man-getter , mm-hmm ♪
♪ I should 've been aware , uh-huh ♪
♪ Of the babysitter ♪ ( shouts )
♪ Should 've the known from the jump Yeah ♪
♪ She was a man-getter Yeah , she was ♪
( indistinct radio chatter )
Improved Synced by BanglarBagh